http://www.ncco.org/privacy

DONATESUBSCRIBEPURCHASE TICKETS
PRIVACY POLICY 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?When you make a donation, as part of the transaction process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our organization or upcoming events. 2 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, or sign up for our mailing list, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@ncco.org or mailing us at:NEW CENTURY CHAMBER ORCHESTRA1668 Bush St San Francisco, CA 941093 - DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Use. 4 - SQUARESPACEOur website is hosted on Squarespace. Your data is stored through Squarespace’s data storage, databases and the general Squarespace application.For more insight, you may also want to read the Squarespace Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here:http://www.squarespace.com/terms-of-service/http://www.squarespace.com/privacy/5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our shop’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.LinksWhen you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.6 - BLOG COMMENTS AND USER CONTENT POSTED TO THE WEBSITEIf you post any Comments or User Content on the Website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to provide there may be read, collected, or used by other users of the Website, as well as other third parties. We are not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these forums. We cannot guarantee that other users have not made copies of and/or will not use such information outside of the Website. We are not responsible for information you choose to post in this forum.7 - SOCIAL MEDIAThe Website provides users the opportunity to interact and post content through various social media sites including, but not limited to, Twitter, Facebook, Google+, Instagram, Dropbox, Tumblr, foursquare, Flickr, YouTube and Vimeo. Your interactions with such tools, and any information you provide in connection with these interactions are publicly viewable outside of the Website domain. Each social media site has its own privacy policies which may be more or less protective than this Policy. If you do not wish for this information to be disclosed, then you should not use these tools. We are not responsible for information you choose to post in this forum.Our site also includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.8 - SECURITYWe store all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of industry-standard access controls. Secure passwords, SSL encryption, disk-based encryption, firewalls, and other measures are in place that helps us to protect your data. However, no company, including Squarespace, can fully eliminate security risks associated with the transmission of personal information through online transactions, and you do so at your own risk.9 - COOKIESNCCO website is built using Squarespace.com for more information on cookies that may be stored on your computer, please refer to its privacy policies:http://www.squarespace.com/privacy/ 10 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.11 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.If our shop is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.12 - QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@ncco.org> or by mail at:NEW CENTURY CHAMBER ORCHESTRA1668 Bush St San Francisco, CA 94109
Sign up with your email address to receive news and updates.
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Sign Up
Thank you!
DONATE
SUBSCRIBE
PrivacyPressCONTACT
COPYRIGHT © 2017 NEW CENTURY CHAMBER ORCHESTRAweb design by beauchamp | artist services
